reel.com 2002-06-02

# Reel.com: Privacy Policy

_Updated: March 15, 2002_

Reel.com created this privacy statement to describe our commitment to your privacy. We seek to protect your private information so that you have a pleasurable viewing experience on our Web site. We will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. We welcome and encourage questions, comments, and suggestions. If you have questions or comments, please contact us at [privacy@reel.com](mailto:privacy@reel.com). 

This policy discusses the following topics: 

  * Personally Identifiable Information  
_What It Is, Where We Collect It, How We Use It, and To Whom We Disclose It_  

  * Cookies  
_What A Cookie Is and How We Use Them_  

  * Children  
_Our Policy For Guests Under Age 18_  

  * Privacy Organizations  
_TrustE and Enonymous_  

  * Choices You Have  
_How to Update Your Personally Identifiable Information, Cancel Your Subscription to Our Newsletter, or Disable Cookies_  

  * Changes to this Privacy Policy  
_Information about Additions and Deletions to this page_  

  * Contact Information  
_How You Can Contact Us_  

**Personally Identifiable Information**

_What Personally Identifiable Information Is_  
Personally identifiable information is your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. 

_Where We Collect Personally Identifiable Information_  
Reel.com collects personally identifiable information when you (1) subscribe to our newsletter, (2) enter sweepstakes, trivia, or other contests, and (3) submit feedback, questions, or "contact us" messages. 

For more information about where we collect personally identifiable information, please click here. 

_How We Use Personally Identifiable Information_  
Reel.com uses your personally identifiable information to personalize your experience on our Web site and to contact you. 

Reel.com also compiles aggregate data from all of our customers to prepare internal reports about which Web pages are popular, how many total unique users visit our site, and different traffic patterns on the site. Reel.com does not combine your personally identifiable information with information about Web pages visited, purchases made, or any other clickstream data. 

For more information about how we use personally identifiable information, please click here. 

_Who We Disclose Personally Identifiable Information To_  
Reel.com will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. Reel.com may disclose some personal information to outside companies who help Reel.com with the administration and delivery of newsletters, promotional games, trivia contests, and sweepstakes. For example, a company who administers a sweepstakes for us may use your e-mail address to update you on your status in the sweepstakes. Or, our newsletters may be distributed by another company that will use your e-mail or shipping address for delivery. We do not allow these outside companies to use this information for any reason other than ones we specifically authorize. 

The Reel.com Web site contains links to other Web sites. Although we **do not** provide any personally identifiable information to these companies, we cannot guarantee your privacy once you leave the Reel.com Web site. Reel.com is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of Web sites with links on our site. Also, shopping services for our customers are now provided by Amazon.com through a link on our site. When you make a purchase, you will enter your personally identifiable information directly on the Amazon.com Web site. Reel.com's privacy policy will not apply on Amazon.com's Web site. You should review Amazon.com's privacy policy if you choose to make purchases. 

Aggregate statistical data gathered from customers, but NOT personally identifiable information, may be shared with our Associate Program associates in order to calculate referral information. Reel.com may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to Reel.com or others. 

For more information about the disclosure of personally identifiable information to select companies, please click here. 

**Cookies**

_What A Cookie Is_  
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies store information about your use of a particular Web site or service and are typically used to make services more convenient and personalized. Most cookies are "session cookies," which are automatically deleted whenever you leave a Web site, although some cookies remain on your computer until you remove them. 

_How We Use Cookies_  
We use cookies (1) to estimate the number of visitors to our Web site, (2) to measure general traffic patterns, (3) to help us determine which of our Associate Program associates make customer referrals, and (4) to track the number of times you see the newsletter sign-up popup window. 

Companies that place ads on the Reel.com Web site — including, but not limited to 24/7 Real Media, DoubleClick, X10, Avenue A, Mediaplex, Ascendo, and Advertisting.com — may also use their own cookies to help determine the frequency and placement of particular ads (please see Advertising). It is possible that some parts of the Reel.com site may not function properly if your browser is set to refuse our cookies. 

For more information about cookies, how we use them, and how to access your browser's cookie settings, please click here. 

**Children**   
_Our Policy For Guests Under Age 18_

Reel.com is committed to protecting the privacy of children. Each visitor confirms that he or she is at least 18 years of age upon registration for our newsletter or one of our sweepstakes. Visitors under age 18 should not submit any personally identifiable information to Reel.com. 

Hollywood Entertainment Corporation believes that parents should supervise their children's online activites and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that may help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools may also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission. 

**Privacy Organizations**  
_TRUSTe and Enonymous.com_  
Reel.com's Web site privacy is reviewed by the following organizations:

_TRUSTe_  
Reel.com is a member of [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html), (www.truste.com) an independent Internet watchdog organization that monitors Web sites' compliance with their posted privacy policies. The TRUSTe seal on the Reel.com Web site further guarantees our commitment to maintaining a secure and private dialogue with our customers. 

_Enonymous.com_  
[Enonymous.com](http://www.enonymous.com/) (www.enonymous.com) rated Reel.com as a 4-Star Privacy Site. 

For more information about other Web sites with online privacy information, please click here. 

**Choices You Have**  
_How to Update Your Personally Identifiable Information, Cancel Your Subscription to Our Newsletter, or Disable Cookies_

_How To Update Your Personally Identifiable Information_  
To update or change the personally identifiable information you gave us, send an email with the new information to [privacy@reel.com](mailto:privacy@reel.com). 

_How To Cancel Your Subscription to Our Newsletter_  
If you wish to unsubscribe from the Hollywood NewsReel mailing list, please [Click Here](http://host1.4at7.net/cgi-bin/a2bv/host_pages/rel/unsub/en_rel.html). 

_Cookie Notification and Disabling_  
Most browsers permit you to set the browser to accept, reject, or notify you of cookie use. However, some parts of the Reel.com Web site may not function properly if your browser is set to reject cookies.   
Some of the companies that place advertisements on our site allow you to "opt-out" of receiving their cookies:  
For DoubleClick's "Opt-Out" link, please [Click Here](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy/opt-out.asp).  
For Avenue A's "Opt-Out" link, please [Click Here](http://www.avenuea.com/info/prBlockingCookies.asp).  
For Media Plex's "Opt-Out" link, please [Click Here](http://www.mediaplex.com/mp/privacy/privacy_f.html).  
For additional information about the 24/7 Real Media privacy policy, please [Click Here](http://www.247media.com/privacy.html).  

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please return to this page from time to time, as we will be updating this statement as our services continue to grow. If we make substantial changes in the way we collect or use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages prior to implementation. 

**Contact Information**

Please direct questions, comments, and suggestions regarding this statement to Hollywood Entertainment Corporation, Legal Dept., 9275 Peyton Lane, Wilsonville, OR 97070.
